Heat.
Owl
boy, come dry me off.
Start rubbing me dry. And don't you dare
miss a spot.
Since you're going to be away on your
work trip all weekend, Shrimpo, I wanted
to make your favorites for lunch. French
fries from the freezer with extra salt
and three room temperature weenies on
forks. Does it make you happy to know
that I listen?
>> Why would I care about something like
that?
>> Hey Finn, will you come over here for a
sec?
Why do you let Shrimpo just walk all
over you like that?
>> What are you talking about? Shrimpo's my
best friend. Last I checked, friends
don't call each other towel boy and make
them wipe down each other's boy bits.
Well, then I guess Shrimpo and I are
just closer than a lot of others think.
>> Fishbowl [__] who are you talking to?
>> Oh, nobody.
>> You are lying to me. Do you want an ass
whooping? Get over here now.
Ah.
Well, well, well. Are you four queens
going to tell me why you were spying on
me through my window if you wanted to
look at the goods? And by goods, I mean
my fat ass cheeks. You know, all you
need to do is ask. But I ain't cheap.
You're the one who said we could see you
off before your weekend long space trip,
but you and Finn didn't show up for the
Uber, so we figured you'd forgot. So, we
decided to stop by your home and pick
you up and take you to your rocket ship.
>> Isn't Goob coming to see me off, too?
Since I'm going to be gone all weekend,
you know.
>> Scrap said over the phone that Goo will
be running late, so she's dropping him
off at the park to meet us.
>> I'm afraid we only have room in the car
for one more tune.
>> That's fine. Finn is pretty much
luggage, so he's going to ride in the
trunk. I'm scared of the dark. I don't
want to ride in the trunk.
So, what time will goo be there to meet
us?
>> Why do you keep asking that?
>> Cuz I hate being caught off guard. I
like to be ready for things, that's all.
Seems like somebody's recently caught a
bad case of the homosexuality that's
been going around town.
>> I am NOT GAY. I hate Goob. I hate you,
too.
>> Easy, Shrimpo. Sprout isn't being
serious.
>> Look, I brought homemade sandwiches for
Shrimpo to eat up in space.
>> Oh, those look so good, Dandy. I'm
jealous. Me and Cosmo have all these
leftover cupcakes and cookies so he can
have them for dessert. Shrimpo, where's
your spaceship? Is it really big? This
will be our first time seeing it.
>> Oh, uh, of course it's big. NASA gave it
to me, you know, since I'm really good
at being an astronaut.
>> Shrimpo, don't forget the fish sticks I
made for your work lunch.
Oh my gosh, fish sticks are my favorite.
Look, Shrimpo, I made you some space
watermelon. Well, I guess right now it's
normal watermelon, but it will be the
space kind after you take it with you.
As you can see, I cut them myself with
my favorite shrimpshaped cookie cutter.
Don't they look like little versions of
you?
>> I don't completely hate them, so I guess
they are acceptable.
Wow, look, that must be Shrimpo's rocket
ship. Back away. Nobody is allowed near
my spaceship. Don't you want to show it
off? Something about this smells fishy.
And I'm not talking about Shrimpo's. A
rocket ship should be a whole lot bigger
than this.
>> You know, it's because it's covered in
space radiation. If you stand next to
it, you'll get space cancer.
>> Then how do you ride it?
>> Because I wear a spaceuit. Are you
mentally challenged?
>> You're not wearing your spaceuit right
now, though.
>> Well, that's true. But I've been to
space so much that space radiation
doesn't affect me.
>> That's so cool. I'm still smelling
something fishy here. And I'm not
talking about Shrimpo's.
>> I don't care what you think. I got to go
to work. Finn, fetch me my spaceuit.
I want to go out there and watch the
rocket ship take off. We can't though.
Shrimpo said that the flames that come
out of the rocket are so bright that
just the sight of it will make our
eyeballs explode. That's why I brought
sunglasses.
[__] I freaking called it. The rocket
ship is made of cardboard. That dirty
shrimp creature lied to us.
>> You're not supposed to be here.
>> Look, Shrimpo ate all his space snacks
already. But what about when he gets to
space?
>> I don't think this gay [__] is going to
space at all.
>> Daddy, what's going on? He's not an
astronaut. That's what's going on. We've
been quite frankly bamboozled. No, I
just needed to eat all of the stupid
food you guys brought me before getting
on board because there wasn't enough
room for it.
>> And yet it can somehow fit your fat butt
cheeks. You don't have to lie to us,
Shrimpo.
>> Okay, fine. I'm I'm not really an
astronaut, okay? I don't work for NASA
and I don't own a rocket ship. Well, are
you any happier now that you have that
information? You've been lying to us for
14 years. For what? What about all the
money you get for going to space on the
weekends? You tell us all the time that
you're a billionaire. Finn, I've got
like six bucks to my name. And the truth
is, I'm a plumber who unclogs poop out
of toilets for a living. But you know,
my toilet is full of a lot of poop and
has been clogged for weeks. I told you
that. And you never offered to push down
all my poopy. You know, there's only
like 40 tunes in all of Garden View.
Eventually, word would get out that
you're just a plumber if you got around
to unclogging all our toilets. So, where
do you go for the time that you're
supposed to be in space?
>> I just walk around that section of
Walmart where they sell paint supplies
for like 4 hours since nobody ever goes
there.
>> Hearing that straight from your mouth
makes me want to beat you up so bad. So,
you've never been on the moon? Not once
in your life. You gave me space rocks
last week.
>> Those were just rocks I found in the
park across the street. They were kind
of abnormal looking, so I knew you would
fall for it.
>> I cannot believe this.
>> Get the hell off me. Cosmos, stop. He'll
get what's coming to his ass at the
public execution tomorrow.
>> Public execution? You know the laws that
revolve around lying in Garden View
better than everybody, Shrimpo. When a
tune is caught, having lied about the
same thing for at least four consecutive
months, they are two face public
execution as punishment. We do that
instead of sending them to jail because
we tunes are too lazy to build a jail
house. It's 4:00 a.m. now, which means
you've got exactly 24 hours before the
execution is set to happen. Girly pop, I
got to hurry back to tell the town
what's going on so we can be prepared
for this afternoon. Start cleaning that
[__] up. As mayor, the only thing I hate
more than liars in my town are [__] ass
tunes who can't even pick up after
themselves.
>> What do you want me to do with your
cardboard rocket shrimpo?
>> Why do you think I would give a [__]
I'm not even going to be here tomorrow.
>> Hey, Shrimpo. I saw you didn't eat all
of my watermelon shrimps. What do you
say we finish off the rest together?
You want to give me diarrhea and make me
rain hot poopy over all the tunes below
me as I'm hung from the gallows tonight?
I'm not eating your dirty rotten
watermelon.
You didn't have to hit him, Shrimpo.
We're all trying to cope with your early
demise.
>> [__]
Hey, piss bag. I shouldn't have yelled
at your ass. I don't like when you hit
me, but it's my own fault for suggesting
to eat watermelon at a bad time anyway.
>> I'm the one who lied about being an
astronaut, so I deserve whatever
punishment you all want to give me. I
ain't [__] I just hate when tunes see
me like a loser and look down on me.
>> I never looked at you like you were a
loser. And I know what it's like to have
everybody look down on you. Nobody takes
my autism seriously or they think that
I'm annoying or faking it all for
attention when it's not either of those.
They think it's all I am. I don't know.
Maybe it is all I am. I just messed
things up.
>> No, you don't. You didn't mess anything
up today. You made some damn good
watermelon shrimps today, which I should
have been more appreciative about.
Now, what's taking those sexy boys so
long?
Hey, don't the fireflies kind of look
like stars?
>> I guess I can kind of see it if I squint
a little bit.
>> If you're going to be executed tomorrow,
then let's go to space right now.
>> We can't.
>> Sure we can. See, all I got to do is
pick you up like this, and now you're
basically in space.
>> We're still way too close to the ground
for this to be considered space.
>> Not if you use your imagination.
Go on, Shrimpo. Give it a whirl.
Your room is so cool at night. It's like
we're really in space.
>> You don't have to tell me things I
already know.
>> Well, did you know there's stars in the
ocean, too? They're called starfish.
>> That sounds like some [__]
>> It's true. Someday I'm going to take you
to the bottom of the ocean so that I can
show you for real.
>> Sounds like a waste of my time. I hate
the ocean.
Oh my golly gosh.
>> Can I kiss you again? even though we're
both boys.
>> I mean, I don't know if it's something
two boys are supposed to do. My sister
would be mad at me if she found out. But
you're my best friend, and it makes me
happy, so
I wouldn't mind.
Finn, your therapy session is in 10
minutes.
>> I'll be right out there, Boxton. I
assume you're all here for the same
reason then. Finn, yada, Louis, and
Blot. Squirm, it's about Shrimpo's
public execution, right? Squirm and the
circus trio. You four are rather recent
additions to Garden View, so this will
be your first public execution. But they
happen quite often because Mayor Dandy
is a mean little flowery [__] so I
assure you that you'll get used to them
in time. And Finn, I know you and
Shrimpo were especially close, like in
the gay kind of way.
>> Would you believe me if I said I thought
we were closer, Boxton? Would you like
to tell us what you were doing in the
bathroom?
>> I was I was hurting myself.
>> Haha, loser alert. We got a jester
maxing little pickme over here.
>> Finn, I think you've become accustomed
to being hurt by others. In this case,
Shrimpo. So much so that it feels wrong
when you're not being hurt. So, you
start hurting yourself as a means to
cope. I think Shrimpo and you being
separated between the veil of earth and
hell. Since we all know hell is where
Shrimpo will be going, we'll actually do
you some good and remind you that you
can be your own tune.
>> Sorry I'm late. I was uh in the backseat
of Shrimpo's Honda Civic for 45 minutes.
>> Me, too. I was also in the uh back seat
of the Honda Civic.
>> Unfortunately, you're a second too late
as our time is up. We'd all better move
our fat dump trucks down to the Walmart
Super Center where Shrimpo's execution
is scheduled. Shrimpo, can we all ride
in the front of your Honda Civic? Take
notice that I said the front exclusively
since I don't want anyone sitting back
there and risk getting a physical
transmitted disease.
>> Pull over. There's something I got to
do.
>> What are you doing? Taking a detour into
the gym? Shouldn't you be going to your
own execution? I want to be sweaty and
glistening when I go out so everybody
knows I lived my life to the fullest.
You're mad about something, aren't you?
Well, be a tune and come out and say it
then, gay boy. You don't have long, you
know.
>> Shrimpo, I've got something I've been
meaning to do for a very long time.
>> What do you want? We've always been a
duo. And now here at the end, I see that
I was the one putting way more effort
into our friendship than you ever were.
>> Okay?
>> You always treated me like dirt, walked
all over me, and worst of all, you never
reciprocated these feelings of love for
you that you know I have.
>> Okay?
>> And that's why I'm challenging you to a
fight so I can break these chains.
>> You little [__] What makes you think
you have any right?
>> All tunes have equal rights in this
town, even if you don't like that. Well,
then take your shirt off.
>> Why?
>> Cuz I want to leave bruises on you as a
lasting image of what happened to the
punk ass [__] who messed with me
while I was alive.
Hurry up, you son of a [__] That was a
cheap shot.
>> I see you put them up fast. Looks like
all the times I beat your ass paid off.
I trained you well without even meaning
to. You never trained me. This is
everything I learned myself. Just trying
to survive all those years with you.
>> Go. Super shrimp piss attack.
You like playing with piss then, huh?
Piss boy. Well, two can pee out of their
balls.
Why? Why would you give your body to Goo
before me? I've been your friend for a
whole lot longer.
>> Does the reason matter when I won't be
here tomorrow? Any answer I give will
only make you want to ask more
questions? Questions? I can't give you
the answers for cuz I'll be gone. But
for starters, Goob's packing a dump
truck while you're built like a twig.
Why do you two smell like each other's
pee?
>> What do you godamn think?
>> Welcome [__] to the public execution
of Shrimpo the shrimp. He has been found
guilty on one count of lying to our
asses for 14 years straight about having
a job at NASA. Before I go any further,
I would like to say thank you everybody
for dressing up in accordance to the
space theme which I personally requested
in the invitations as a means to
humiliate Shrimpo. Further, the
execution style was determined based on
the nature of the lie. As we learned
that he hides his lies of never actually
having been to space by hiding in the
paint section of the Walmart Super
Center, we figured it'd be best that he
meets his demise in the very same place.
We will be submerging his head upside
down in a bucket of paint for 8 hours
until he's not breathing anymore. I'm
sure he'll stop breathing in like 6 or 7
minutes. Aha! 67? Yeah, 67.
>> Astro, don't do that.
Dial, put the torch out. They're a fire
hazard.
>> You literally told me to start passing
out the torches at 6:00 p.m.
>> That was when the location was going to
be outside. Obviously, I don't want them
anymore.
>> What the hell did I just say?
>> Again, they are here because you told me
specifically to bring them here. See
everybody, this is what Dandy always
does. You all saw it. No, what they saw
just now is you being an idiot. Can I
give you words and then they change me
to come to me so we can reaffirm what we
will do next to?
>> Good golly, what's going on? Why aren't
the sliding doors working?
The fire is burning the electrical
circuits. We're all stuck inside like
sardines.
>> What are we going to do, Sprout? I'm so
scared. Calm your tits, [__] boy.
There's got to be some place for us to
get out of here. Wait, Shrimpo space
rocks. Or should I say earth rocks? What
are you doing? If I throw these rocks
hard enough at the windows, I should be
able to free us.
[__] I missed. It's fine, though. I
still got two rocks left. [__] I
missed. Make sure you've got good aim on
this one. I'm going to go stand there in
the corner.
>> [__] I missed. What are you doing,
Seedley?
>> What's it look like? I'm trying to break
a hole in the window so we can climb
out, but I'm all out of rocks.
>> If I may suggest, Dandy is the same
weight as like five bowling balls. If we
can both lift him together and toss him
at the window, it would be the
equivalent of throwing a bowling ball
five times bigger than normal bowling
balls.
I'm sorry. I can't throw him any further
than just a couple inches.
>> Don't apologize, Dial. It's not our
fault. Dandy is too fat to be of use for
anything.
I just checked the back of the store and
the doors are open, so we can get out
that way. Hop on this mobility scooter
and we'll be home free.
We lost the town Walmart, but at least
everybody was able to get out. This will
surely be a public execution that will
be remembered for years to come. I'm
going to miss Shrimpo.
What is all this? Why are all you losers
cheering for me? Because you saved us,
Shrimpo. I did? How did I do that?
Shrimpo, don't you get it? It was your
space rocks that saved us. You're a
hero. I tried throwing them at the
window, but kept accidentally hitting
others instead. And that led to me and
Dial picking up Dandy to try and throw
him at the window, but that didn't work
either. So Astro went looking on the
other end of the store for an exit and
he found one and we were able to get
out.
>> I I see. Well, [__] I guess that does
make me a hero, doesn't it? And you
can't public execute a hero. Damn. I got
my holes obliterated by goo this
morning. And now I'm not going to be
executed anymore. This is the best
godamn day of my life.
There he goes, the town hero. Yep.
>> You two losers live in a cardboard box.
>> Goob, what is Shrimpo doing here?
>> I wanted to invite him over for dinner.
No offense, Shrimpo, but Goob. You
really think it's a good idea to be
friends with him?
>> What is that disgusting sewer water
you're boiling?
>> It's our special craft siblings stew.
Scraps makes it everyday, and sometimes
I help.
>> It's just water with a lot of salt. We
rarely have anything else to put in it.
I mean, we had half a watermelon we
found in the dumpster over the weekend,
but well, Goob was adamant about giving
it to you this morning, so I let him do
that. If it's stew you're making, then
I'll run to my HOUSE AND GRAB SOME
potatoes and also carrots.
>> You don't have to do that. We're the
ones treating you.
>> That's surprisingly nice for you,
Shrimpo.
>> Shut up. I'm going to hate it
regardless, but if I'm going to eat it,
I'm at least going to make it tolerable.
Let's go, Goob.
>> Get out. I don't want to hurt you.
>> Stop. Stop it. Where will Goop and I
live if you destroy our home?
>> Goob took everything from me, so it's
only fair I get to take everything from
him, too.
Don't hurt my sister.
>> What the hell is going on outside?
>> Finn, stop it. You are embarrassing me.
>> You're the one who caused the shrimpo. I
wouldn't be doing this if it weren't for
you.
>> You can't blame me for this.
>> Shrimpo Finn, it's not this serious. We
can work it all out.
>> Okay, I just got to say what we're all
thinking in the most non-offensive way
possible. Shrimpo is not a good enough
catch to warrant all this drama.
>> I should congratulate you for winning.
Oh boy, I won something. I've had enough
of you using your autism to play stupid.
You toon stealer. Toon stealer. What do
you see in Shrimpo? Oh, this is about
him. Shrimpo is always hurting on the
inside. Nobody likes him, so he lashes
out because it's the only way he knows
how to show his frustration with
everything. And when he does, people
either push him away or they just take
it and let him hit him. Is that last bit
supposed to be a jab at me? You don't
know what it's like when he hits me. You
don't know our friendship. My hugs can
make everyone happy. So, I know if I hug
him a whole lot, he can be fixed. If I
let go the second he pushes, then I'm
just doing to him what everyone else
does.
>> Finn's become totally twisted.
>> Boxton.
>> When a tune becomes overtaken completely
by one negative emotion, they become the
worst version of themselves. It looks
like Finn here has become overtaken by
his jealousy of Goop getting to Shrimpo
before he could.
Shrimpo.
Absolute containment. Purple box.
Purple box. Cataclysm core.
Heat. Heat.
Hey, uh, Finn, it's Shrimpo again before
you start crying or whatever. Yeah, I'm
sorry things blew up after me and Goob
hooked up. I didn't call to make you
feel better or anything. This whole
situation's just been exhausting for me,
you know. And honestly, I'd rather do
this face to face because over the
phone, you sound extra pathetic when
you're upset. I guess I value your
friendship a little, like super super
small. But I guess it is there or some
[__] So, IF YOU WANT, I CAN COME OVER
when you stop acting like a little
[__] Goob can come too, but that's
your call. I can't really say at the
moment what I even want with Goob
because somehow choosing between you and
him turned into this giant annoying
problem in my life. I just need time to
figure it out. Like you do, too.
Damn. At this rate, Shrimpo is going to
be pulling so many [__] there won't
be any for the rest of us. Sprout,
you're never going to believe what I
just learned. What? Did you know only
like 1 percentage of people who watch a
Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 video are subscribed?
That's quite frankly bananas. Are the
other 99% mentally challenged? I don't
know. But since making Dy's World
cartoons, Tamer's been getting like
5,000 subscribers with every upload. I
bet if we tell the viewers to subscribe
and they actually do it like good little
[__] Tamers would hit like 100,000
subscribers really fast. That would be
cool. Hey sexy [__] tell you what.
If you subscribe to Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 and
we hit 100,000 subscribers, Tamers 1 2 3
4 5 will do a face reveal and blow you
away with how sexy he is. Hey, Tamer
said nothing about doing that. What if
the fans react the same way they did to
Dream where they called him ugly?
Exactly. Face reveals only work if the
YouTuber is sexy. And the difference
between Dream and Tamers is that Tamers
is sexy. Also, I'll hold Dandy down and
kiss him right on the lips for 20
minutes. We are not doing that. What?
Would it not be worth it for 100,000
subscribers? I mean, I guess it would be
kind of worth it. Well, there you have
it, [__] 100,000 subscribers and
you'll be getting a tamer's face reveal
and also the best godamn makeout session
between a strawberry and a flower with
gay colored petals you've ever seen.